bizzdesign.fr 2019-07-14

# Privacy Policy - BiZZdesign

#### I. GENERAL

As BiZZdesign Holding BV and its subsidiaries (“BiZZdesign”), we collect personal data of our customers, prospective customers and of the visitors of our website while providing our services along with sourcing your contact information from our trusted business partners. On several pages on our website, you will be asked to enter your personal data.

As BiZZdesign we take the privacy of our customers and all other people that are connected with BiZZdesign, i.e. through our website, or in any other way, very seriously. BiZZdesign takes every effort to process and store the personal data that you enter during visits to BiZZdesign’s website in such a manner that your privacy is protected and ensured.

This privacy policy describes how BiZZdesign gathers, uses, shares and protects personal information. In this policy, “personal information” or “personal data” means any information about an identifiable individual.

BiZZdesign may amend this Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on our website. All amended terms automatically take effect on the date set out in the posted policy, unless otherwise specified.

#### II. COOKIES

In addition to personal data, BiZZdesign uses cookies, if required on special parts of our website. A cookie is a small file that a server stores on your hard disk and can only be recognized by the server that saved the cookie. A cookie shows our server that you have returned to a particular page on our website.. We use cookies and similar tools to gather information during your visit to our website, such as your IP address (a number that is assigned to your computer when you are surfing on the Internet), and the date and the time of your visit to our website. We use this information pursuant to our legitimate business interests to provide our services and/or to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. More information about the use of cookies can be found in our [cookie policy](https://bizzdesign.com/cookie-policy/).  If you so wish, you can configure in your browser that cookies are refused or you are warned when cookies are sent. Information collected by cookies can be used to generate statistics about the website, in order to assess the use of the website anonymously and in terms of total figures and to optimize the website and the solutions and services offered to customers.

#### III. USING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION – PURPOSES AND USE

BiZZdesign uses the data we collect for:

Services. BiZZdesign processes your personal data to be able to deliver our services to you or the company you work for. We use the data, for example, to send an invoice or maintain our relationship with you.

Engagement of third parties. BiZZdesign may engage other parties to perform (part of) our services to you. To the extent that these third parties need access to personal data to perform such services, BiZZdesign has taken the appropriate contractual and organizational measures to ensure that your data are processed exclusively for the purposes specified in this privacy policy and in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations.

Marketing and sales activities. As a customer of BiZZdesign, we are happy to make offers for our products and services. We may do this by phone, email or mail. You can always opt out of receiving emails from us by entering your email address [HERE](https://go.bizzdesign.com/email-preferences).

Processing of your data on BiZZdesign website. We collect and use your personal data on our website to deliver our (web) services and communicate with you. Your data are also used for research and analysis to improve our services and our websites. We may also use your data entered on our websites in certain cases to send information by e-mail about other services of BiZZdesign to you, provided that we are legally entitled to send you such e-mails.

Recruitment purposes. We allow you to submit your CV for general applications, to apply for specific jobs or to subscribe to our job alerts. Your CV will be stored in a database managed and controlled by BiZZdesign. BiZZdesign may use a third party to host the service, application, and database. BiZZdesign will engage with the third party as according to the “Engagement of third parties” paragraph above.

#### IV. LEGAL BASIS FOR PROCESSING

We use all the personal data mentioned above to implement and process the agreement with you, for example, when you request us to provide a service. We may also have a statutory obligation to process your personal data, for example, to fulfill our obligations under tax law.

We can also use your personal data because we have legitimate interests in doing so. Among these interests are providing a good service, protecting financial interests, personnel planning and keeping our customers informed about our new and existing products and services.

If we process personal data on the basis of your consent, we will ask you for this separately. You may always subsequently withdraw consent, but in such a case the data processed prior to the moment of withdrawal will remain lawful.

#### V. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We do not share your personal data with third parties unless one of the following circumstances applies:

With your explicit consent. We may share your personal data with third parties when we have your consent to do so.

For external processing by third parties engaged by us. We may provide your personal data to our subsidiaries or other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in

accordance with our privacy policy and any other appropriate obligations of confidentiality and security measures.

For legal reasons. We may share your personal data with third parties if we have a good-faith belief that access to and use of the personal data is reasonably necessary to (i) meet any applicable law, regulation, and/or court order; (ii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; and/or iii) protect the interests, properties or safety of BiZZdesign, our users or the public as far as in accordance with the law.

#### VI. STORAGE PERIOD

BiZZdesign does not store your personal data longer than is legally permitted and necessary for the purposes for which the data were collected. The storage period depends on the nature of the information and the purposes of processing.

#### VII. ACCESS, RECTIFICATION AND DELETING AND RIGHT TO OBJECT

BiZZdesign offers you access to the personal data we process. This means you can contact us asking us to inform you about your personal data that we have collected and processed and the purposes such data are used for. If you believe we are holding inaccurate personal data, please contact us so we can correct the data. You may also ask us to delete your personal data from our systems. We will comply with such request unless we have a legitimate ground to not delete the data within a reasonable timescale.

You may object to the certain use of your personal data if such data are processed for other purposes than necessary for the performance of our services or for compliance with a legal obligation. You may also object any further processing of your personal data after prior given consent. If you object to the further processing of your personal data, this may lead to fewer possibilities to use our websites and other services.

You have the right to withdraw your consent at all times.

You also have the right to file in a complaint at [privacy@bizzdesign.com](mailto:privacy@bizzdesign.com).

For any inquiries about this policy, you may contact BiZZdesign, Corporate Security Officer, Capitool 15, (7521 PL) Enschede, the Netherlands or [privacy@bizzdesign.com](mailto:privacy@bizzdesign.com).
